美国华纳兄弟娱乐公司
美国艾肯娱乐公司
索尼电影娱乐公司
美国哥伦比亚电影公司
复制人
是泰瑞公司研制的生物工程人类，被用于世外殖民地
它们力量过人，是理想的劳动力
在一系列的暴乱之后，复制人的生产遭禁，泰瑞公司破产
21世纪20年代中叶，生态系统崩溃，企业家尼安德·华莱士由此发迹
他的人造农业专利避免了饥荒发生
华莱士收购了泰瑞公司的残部，研发出新一代服从命令的复制人
许多寿命无限的旧型号复制人连锁8型幸存了下来
他们被追捕，被"退休"
追捕他们的人依然叫做
银 翼 杀 手
加利福尼亚州     2049年
洛杉矶警局
自动驾驶模式
希望你不介意我冒昧进来
I hope you don't mind me taking the liberty.
我特地注意了  没弄脏地板
I was careful not to drag in any dirt.
脏了我也不介意
I don't mind the dirt.
但我介意
I do mind...
不请自来
unannounced visits.
你是警察
You police?
你是萨珀·莫顿  序列号NK68514
Are you Sapper Morton? Civic number NK68514?
-我是个农民  -我看到了
- I'm a farmer. - I saw that.
那你种什么
What do you farm?
高蛋白蠕虫
It's a protein farm.
华莱士的技术
Wallace design.
锅里煮的这个
Is that what I smell?
我自己种的
Grow that just for me.
大蒜
Garlic.
大蒜啊
尝尝看吧
Go on, try some.
不了  谢谢
No, thank you.
我还是比较想
I prefer to keep an empty stomach
先把麻烦事情解决了再去填饱肚子
until the hard part of the day is done.
你来这儿多久了
How long you been here?
2020年来的
Since 2020.
但你以前并不是农民  对不对
But you haven't always been a farmer, have you?
你的包
Your bag.
那是殖民地医疗包
It's colonial medical use.
是军用品
Military issue.
在哪驻扎  卡兰星
Where were you? Calantha?
那里不好过吧
Must have been brutal.
你要抓我走
Plan on taking me in?
然后给我做个检查
Let them take a look inside?
莫顿先生
Mr. Morton...
我也非常想抓你走
if taking you in is an option...
但可惜的是我也没得选择
I would much prefer that to the alternative.
你知道总会有人送你上路
I'm sure you knew it would be someone in time.
很抱歉  那个人是我
I'm sorry it had to be me.
无所谓了
Good as any.
那么 不介意的话
Now, if you don't mind...
麻烦你往上看再往左看 谢了
if you could just look up and to the left, please.
不 不要站起来
Please don't get up.
杀死同类是什么感觉
How's it feel killing your own kind?
我的同类不会逃跑所以不会被"退役"
I don't retire my own kind because we don't run.
老型号才会逃跑
Only older models do.
你们这些新型号都愿意做这种脏活
And you new models are happy scraping the shit...
因为你们从未见过奇迹
because you've never seen a miracle.
这里全部拍照留证
Just photograph everything.
警督  多谢
Madam, please.
洛杉矶警局将线路来电
Incoming L.A.P.D. Re-codec hash.
洛杉矶警局
受伤了  我不出医药费
You're hurt. I'm not paying for that.
-我会处理  -说吧
- I'll glue it. - And?
是残存的连锁8型之一
One of the tail-end Nexus 8s.
他好像把你伤得不轻
He looks like he could take your head off.
是不轻
He tried.
他在卡兰星开了小差
He went AWOL after Calantha...
还有几个同伙我也不打算放过
with a few more in his outfit I wouldn't mind closing out.
-就他一个  -就他一个
- Just him? - Just him.
回警局做基准测试
Come on home for your baseline.
稍等  长官
One moment, madam.
分析土壤照常30米
Thirty meters to maximum depth.
洛杉矶警局证物
那是什么
What is that?
我派挖掘队去
I'll send a dig team.
要下雨了尽快回来
Come on home before the storm.
洛杉矶警局
KD6-3.7号警官
Officer KD6 - 3.7.
-我们开始吧  准备好了  -好了
- Let's begin. Ready? - Yes, sir.
背诵基准声明
Recite your baseline.
血黑色的虚无开始编织
And blood-black nothingness began to spin.
开始编织一个网络  细胞之间相连
A system of cells interlinked within cells...
再相连  与那主干再相连
interlinked within cells interlinked within one stem.
滚开  假货
Fuck off, skin-job.
趁着那恐怖的黑暗分明可见
And dreadfully distinct against the dark,
洁白水柱向上高喷
a tall white fountain played.
-细胞  -细胞
- Cells. - Cells.
创伤后基线测试
警官KD6-3.7
2049年6月30日
-你是否为某机构服务过  细胞  -细胞
- Have you ever been in an institution? Cells. - Cells.
-他们把你关在牢房里吗  细胞  -细胞
- Do they keep you in a cell? Cells. - Cells.
不执行任务时
When you're not performing your duties,
-他们是否把你关在小房间里  细胞  -细胞
- do they keep you in a little box? - Cells.
-相连  -相连
- Interlinked. - Interlinked.
握着你所爱之人的手是何感觉  相连
What's it like to hold the hand of someone you love? Interlinked.
相连
Interlinked.
他们是否教过你感觉手指相触  相连
Did they teach you how to feel finger to finger? Interlinked.
相连
Interlinked.
你是否渴望与人心心相连  相连
Do you long for having your heart interlinked? Interlinked.
相连
Interlinked.
-你是否梦想过心心相连  -相连
- Do you dream about being interlinked? - Interlinked.
把女儿抱在怀中是什么感受  相连
What's it like to hold your child in your arms? Interlinked.
相连
Interlinked.
你是否觉得失去了一部分的自己
Do you feel that there's a part of you that's missing?
-相连  -相连
- Interlinked. - Interlinked.
-细胞之间相连  -细胞之间相连
- Within cells interlinked. - Within cells interlinked.
为什么不重复三遍  细胞之间相连
Why don't you say that three times?
细胞之间相连  细胞之间相连
Within cells interlinked. Within cells interlinked.
细胞之间相连
Within cells interlinked.
结束了
We're done.
依然稳定
Constant K.
你可以去拿奖金了
You can pick up your bonus.
谢谢长官
Thank you, sir.
注意  请绕路
Caution, keep clear.
随时随地都可与殖民地通话
Connect to Off-world any time, any place.
20分钟内就会生效
Packages start at 20 minutes.
多种服务可供选择
Many options available.
乔伊满足您的一切幻想  乔伊伴您走遍天涯海角
Joi goes anywhere you want her to go.
随时随地都可与殖民地通话
Connect to Off-world any time, any place.
20分钟内就会生效
Packages start at 20 minutes.
多种服务可供选择
Many options available.
帅气的铁皮兵你怎么了
你现在回来了  笨蛋
谁他妈会在这儿等你
我要把你这个混蛋赶出去
滚
假 货
K  我没听到你回来  今天真早
K? I didn't hear you. You're early.
那你想让我回去吗
You want me to come back?
-快去洗洗吧  -遵命  女士
- Just go scrub. - Yes, ma'am.
工作顺利吗
How was your meeting?
老一套
The usual.
你今天怎样
How was your day?
我得了幽闭症
I'm getting cabin fever.
系使用99.9%解毒液
99.9 percent detoxified water.
工作时出了点意外
I had an accident at work.
衬衣好像烂了
I think I ruined my shirt.
我肯定能帮你补好的  先让我看看吧
I'm sure I can fix that for you. Let me take a look at it.
我想喝杯酒
I need a drink.
-你想喝一杯吗  -帮我倒一杯好吗
- Do you want a drink first? - Pour me one, will you?
我在试验新菜谱
I'm trying a new recipe.
只要多练练就好了
I just need a bit more practice.
别瞎忙活了
Don't fuss.
肉应该多腌一会吧  希望别太干
I should have marinated it longer. I hope it isn't dry.
你知道吗  这首歌是重奏唱片公司在1966年发行的
Did you know this song was released in 1966 on Reprise Records?
是音乐排行榜第一名
It was number one on the charts.
饭马上就做好  我再收个尾就可以了
It won't be much longer. Just putting on the finishing touches.
好啦  做好了  希望你会喜欢
Okay, it's ready. I hope you're gonna like it.
说了别瞎忙活
I told you not to fuss.
但是呢...
And yet....
好啦  用餐愉快
Voilà! Bon appétit.
我很想你  亲爱的
I missed you, baby sweet.
宝贝儿  你做的很好
Honey, it's beautiful.
把你的脚抬起来
Just put your feet up.
放松
Relax.
今天很累  嗯
Was a day?
确实很累
It was a day.
给我念书好吗
Would you read to me?
弗拉基米尔·纳博科夫  《微暗的火》
能让你心情好点
It'll make you feel better.
-你讨厌这本书  -我也不想看这个
- You hate that book. - I don't wanna read either.
我们跳舞吧
Let's dance.
你想跳舞  还是想看看你的礼物
Do you wanna dance, or do you wanna open your present?
什么礼物
What present?
-这个  -今天是什么日子
- This one. - What's the occasion?
这么说吧...
Let's just say...
-是我们的周年纪念日  -是吗
- it's our anniversary. - Is it?
不  但是  我们就假装是吧
No, but let's just say that it is.
好吗
Okay?
周年纪念快乐
Happy anniversary.
显形装置
An emanator.
乔伊
检测到投射仪  正在连接
华莱士
谢谢你
Thank you.
亲爱的  现在你想去哪就能去哪了
Honey, you can go anywhere you want in the world now.
你想先去哪里
Where do you wanna go first?
跟你在一起我好开心
I'm so happy when I'm with you.
你不必这么说
You don't have to say that.
语音信息
正在播放
挖出东西了  有新线索
The dig's come through. We have a new lead.
快来警局
Get down here.
碳含量  14.6GPH
Carbon read: 14.6 GPH.
箱子是士兵个人用品箱
Your box is a military footlocker,
属于萨珀·莫顿
issued to Sapper Morton...
被那个家伙当成骨甍用
creatively repurposed as an ossuary:
也就是尸骨罐
a box of bones.
除了骨头  只有头发
Nothing else in it but hair.
土壤样品表明这个女人已经被埋葬30年了
The soil samples indicate that she's been buried for 30 years.
骨头全都碎了被清洗过
Bones all dismantled, fully cleaned,
放骨头的人很小心
meticulously laid to rest.
"女人"
"She"?
死亡原因  珂珂
Cause of death, Coco?
没有骨折  没有外伤的迹象  只除了...
No breaks, no sign of trauma, except...
髋骨这里有一道裂缝
a fracture through the ilium.
是条很窄的产道  胎儿肯定是被卡住了
It's a narrow birth canal. Baby must have got stuck.
她当时怀孕了
She was pregnant?
她不是被杀的
So he didn't kill her?
她是死于难产
She died in childbirth.
那是什么
What's that?
回放
Go back.
放大
Closer.
再放大
那是什么
What's that?
髂脊上有几道切口
Notching in the iliac crest.
切口精准  像是用的手术刀
It's fine-point, like a scalpel.
看起来像做了个剖腹产手术
That looks like an emergency C-section.
刀口利落  没有挣扎痕迹
The cuts are clean. No sign of a struggle.
莫顿是个军医
He was a combat medic.
也许他想救人  却没救成
Maybe he tried to save her, and he just couldn't.
看不出他会善心大发
He didn't seem like the saving type.
但他退役埋了这个女人
He went to the trouble of burying her.
一个多愁善感的假货
A sentimental skin-job.
抱歉
Sorry.
那个孩子在哪里
So where's the kid?
扫描整个领域了
You scan the whole field?
只有泥土虫子  没有别的尸体
Just dirt and worms. No other bodies.
也许他吃了
Maybe he ate it.
这根本不可能
That's not possible.
她是个复制人
She was a Replicant.
怀孕了
Pregnant.
人和复制人  之间的隔离
The world is built on a wall.
是世界的基石
It separates kind.
告诉他们双方没有差别
Tell either side there's no wall,
会引发战争
you bought a war.
或者屠杀
Or a slaughter.
所以你今天...
So what you saw...
什么都没看到
didn't happen.
是  长官
Yes, madam.
我的工作是维持秩序
It is my job to keep order.
这是我们的职责  维持秩序
That's what we do here. We keep order.
你想我调
You want it gone?
清除一切
Erase everything.
-包括孩子  -所有痕迹
- Even the child? - All trace.
还有什么要说的吗
You have anything more to say?
我还没有清除过自然出生的人
I've never retired something that was born before.
有什么区别
What's the difference?
自然出生的大概有灵魂吧
To be born is to have a soul, I guess.
你要违抗命令
Are you telling me no?
我并没有违抗命令的权利
I wasn't aware that was an option, madam.
那就好
Attaboy.
你没那东西也活得很好
You've been getting on fine without one.
什么东西
What's that, madam?
灵魂
A soul.
你们这些新型号都很愿意做这种脏活
And you new models are happy scraping the shit...
因为你们从未见过奇迹
because you've never seen a miracle.
华莱士公司
地球总部
麻烦帮我查一个序列号
Just checking in on an old serial number.
有DNA信息吗
Confirmation DNA?
有头发
I got hair.
■
抽屉号
噢
oh
是老型号
An old one.
大停电之前的
Pre-Blackout.
干电不好找
That's gonna be tough.
那时的数据不多
Not much from then.
而且全都...
And what's there is...
很难解读
thick milky.
您可以按自己的想法定制
You can customize them as much as you'd like.
只要想  就和真人无异
As human as you want them to be.
但您打算用到钻井工地上  对不对
But your operation is strictly a drill site, isn't it?
我不建议您把钱浪费在
I wouldn't waste your money
智能和情感功能上
on intelligence, attachment or appeal.
除非您想再订购一批情趣型的
Unless you'd like to add some pleasure models to your order.
我们改天再约时间谈  可以吗
Would it be possible to reschedule this call, please?
大家都记得大停电时自己在哪  你呢
Everyone remembers where they were at the Blackout. You?
那时候我还没出厂
That was a little before my time.
我当时和爸妈在一起  然后是十天的黑暗
I was home with my folks, then 10 days of darkness.
所有机器停止运转
Every machine stopped cold.
等电终于来了  数据都没了
When the lights came back, we were wiped clean.
照片  文件  所有的数据...没了
Photos, files, every bit of data, gone.
还有银行记录
Bank records too.
我倒不介意
Didn't mind that.
只有纸质文件保留了下来
It's funny it's only paper that lasted.
有意思  我们什么都放电脑上
I mean, we had everything on drives.
什么都放
Everything, everything, everything.
我妈妈一直可惜我小时候的照片没了
My mom still cries over the lost baby pictures.
可惜  你小时候一定很可爱吧
Well, it's a shame. You must have been adorable.
数据很凌乱  没多少信息
Pretty fractured. Not much on it.
很老的型号  大驱逐之前的
One of the last gens, pre-Prohibition.
是那种标准型
Standard issue.
-泰瑞制造  -还有呢
- Made by Tyrell. - And?
没什么特别的
Unremarkable.
"Unremarkable"?
我们有别的资料给这位警官
There must be something else we can find for him.
又一个迷失的序列号回归了
Another prodigal serial number returns.
30年的悬案总算是解决了
A 30-year-old open case finally closed.
谢谢您  警官
Thank you, officer.
我叫露芙  代表华莱士先生
I'm here for Mr. Wallace. I'm Luv.
你有名字
He named you.
你一定很特别
Must be special.
我代表华莱士先生
I'm here for Mr. Wallace.
跟我来
Follow me.
那些老型号差点毁了所有人的努力
The ancient models give the entire endeavor a bad name.
华莱士先生的贡献  可以说是无可比拟的
What a gift, don't you think, from Mr. Wallace to the world?
如果他没有收购泰瑞公司
The outer colonies would never
并改进技术
have flourished had he not bought Tyrell...
殖民地不会这么繁荣
revivified the technology.
他的贡献并不止于此
To say the least of what we do.
你也是我们的顾客
I see you're also a customer.
对我们的产品满意吗
Are you satisfied with our product?
她确实非常真实  谢谢
She's very realistic. Thank you.
这里  废品都在这里
Here. All the junk is in here.
幸好华莱士先生热爱收集数据
Lucky for you, Mr. Wallace is a data hoarder.
几十年没人来过了
No one's been down here in ages.
我很抱歉
Sorry about that.
这些就是我们的存储器
All our memory bearings from the time.
大停电时都受到了损坏
They were all damaged in the Blackout.
但有一些还是留了下来
But there are sometimes fragments.
泰瑞公司档案
你有个小儿子
You got a little boy.
你给他看蝴蝶标本  和抓蝴蝶的瓶子
He shows you his butterfly collection, plus the killing jar.
我带他去看医生
I'd take him to the doctor.
-突然有一只黄蜂在你手臂上爬行  -我会杀了它
- There's a wasp crawling on your arm. - I'd kill it.
你在看杂志
You're reading a magazine.
突然看到一幅全页的女人裸照
You come across a full-page nude photo of a girl.
这是在测试
Is this testing
复制人还是女同性恋者  戴克先生
whether I'm a Replicant or a lesbian, Mr. Deckard?
请你回答我的问题
Just answer the questions, please.
很难说清她是什么  至少对某人而言
It was unclear what she was, at least to someone.
这是个测试
This was a test.
当时还很难分辨
We were difficult to spot then.
发现她的过程有什么异常吗
Was there anything unusual about how you found her?
以至于要正式调查
To warrant an official investigation?
你知道人类对老型号有多在意
You know how people are about old serial numbers.
知道他们干了什么能让大家睡得更香
Everyone just sleeps better when they know where they got to.
她喜欢那个人
She likes him.
谁
Who?
戴克警官
This Officer Deckard.
她想惹火戴克
She's trying to provoke him.
被问到私人问题能够使人振奋
It is invigorating being asked personal questions.
让人感到
Makes one feel...
被需要
desired.
你喜欢你的工作吗  警官
Do you enjoy your work, officer?
请代我感谢华莱士先生
Please thank Mr. Wallace for your time.
你以前曾经和戴克警官
You worked with Officer Deckard...
一起工作过
back in the day.
你对他了解多少
What can you tell me about him?
他喜欢单独行动
He liked to work alone.
我也是
So did I.
所以我们一起努力保持这种状态
So we worked together to keep it that way.
就是这样
That was it.
你还知道别的什么吗
Anything else you can tell me?
他在这世上长久不了啦
He wasn't long for this world.
为什么
How so?
从他眼睛里能看出来
Something in his eyes.
你知道怎么能联系到他吗
Any idea how I could contact him?
不
None.
他已经退下去了
He's nyugdíjas.
退役了
Retired.
发生了什么
What happened?
大概得偿所愿了吧
Probably got what he wanted.
不被打扰
To be alone.
欢迎回来  先生
Welcome back, sir.
发货之前您想再看看新型号吗
You wanted to review the new model, sir, before shipment?
一个天使永远都不应该不带着礼物
An angel should never enter the kingdom of heaven...
进入天国
without a gift.
你至少可以说"一个婴孩降生"了
Can you at least pronounce, "a child is born"?
新型号啊
A new model.
那么我就看看她吧
Well, let us see her, then.
出生后第一本能
The first thought...
往往是恐惧
one tends to fear...
是保护自己
to preserve the clay.
真是奇妙啊
It's fascinating.
尚未明了自身存在时
Before we even know what we are...
就害怕死亡
we fear to lose it.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
让我好好看看你
Now, let's have a look at you.
我们制造天使
We make angels...
来造福文明社会
in the service of civilization.
是的  过去有过坏天使
Yes, there were bad angels once.
我现在造的是好天使
I make good angels now.
所以人类才能占领九个外星新世界
That is how I took us to nine new worlds.
九个
Nine.
小孩能掰着手指从一数到九
A child can count to nine on fingers.
而我们应该征服宇宙
We should own the stars.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
文明的每一次飞跃都是建立在可支配[一次性的]劳动力的基础上
Every leap of civilization was built off the back of a disposable workforce.
人类不可奴役自己的同类
We lost our stomach for slaves...
所以有了复制人
unless engineered.
但我只能造这么多
But I can only make so many.
不开花  不结果
That barren pasture...
这里是
empty...
贫瘠的天体
and salted...
就是这里
right here.
不过是一片不毛之地
The dead space between the stars.
改变这里  我们才能拥有天国
And this, the seat that we must change for heaven.
我无法让他们生殖  上天作证  我努力过了
I cannot breed them. So help me, I have tried.
我们需要比以往更多的复制人
We need more Replicants than can ever be assembled.
百万  千万  这样人类才能愈发壮大
Millions, so we can be trillions more.
这样我们才能重新占领伊甸园
We could storm Eden and retake her.
泰瑞最后的创新
Tyrell's final trick:
生殖
Procreation.
完美  却丢失了
Perfected, then lost.
但还有一个孩子
But there is a child.
带他来见我
Bring it to me.
是
Sir.
你是最优秀的天使
The best angel of all.
是不是  露芙
Aren't you, Luv?
穿绿夹克的那个人
The man with the green jacket.
是他杀了萨珀  看看他知道什么
The one who killed Sapper. Find out what he knows.
你好  你好  复制货
Hello, hello, A-Boy.
一个人吗
You alone?
他是银翼杀手
我认得他
他很危险  你走不走
没关系  别担心
It's fine.
你不给女士买包烟吗
Wanna buy a lady a cigarette?
你都不笑一下
Oh, you don't even smile.
你刚刚没听到吗
Didn't you hear your friends?
不知道我是什么
Don't you know what I am?
知道
Yeah.
吃米饭的假货
Guy eating rice.
那是什么
What's that?
一棵树
It's a tree.
我以前没见过树
Never seen a tree before.
很漂亮
It's pretty.
它死了
It's dead.
那么谁会留着一棵死树呢
Now, who keeps a dead tree?
你不会杀我的  对吧
You're not gonna kill me, are you?
看情况  你是什么型号
Depends. What's your model number?
你可以看着我的眼睛自己发现
Why don't you look under my eye and find out?
你不喜欢真人
You don't like real girls.
好吧  我一直在这
Well, I'm always here.
这些你不能拿
You can't take those.
我知道  要走正规流程
Of course not. Proper channels and paperwork.
我有文件
It's all here.
帮我拿一下
Hold this for me.
这个  你看吧
Yep. Here you go.
珂珂死了
Coco is dead.
骨头也不见了
Bones are gone.
消息泄露  有人知道了  这才过了多久
It's out. Already out. How long did that take?
你有什么发现吗  别跟我说没有
So, what do you have for me? And don't say nothing.
我找到了那个
I found that.
一只袜子
A sock?
-哪里找到的  -萨珀家
- Where'd you find it? - Sapper's.
还有别的吗
Anything else?
别的我都一把火烧了
I burned everything else.
那这是什么  什么日期
Then what's this? What's that date?
是生日吗  还是死亡日期
Is that a birthday? Is that a death day?
还没查出来
I don't know yet.
难道只有我才知道事情有多严重吗
Am I the only one that can see the fucking sunrise here?
这件事能改变整个世界
This breaks the world, K.
我接触过很多复制人
You know, I've known a lot of your kind.
都很有用  但我有时会忘记你也是
All useful, but with you, I sometimes forget.
我小时候还没有你们复制人
We didn't have any of you where I was a kid.
你记得以前的事吗
Do you remember anything?
来我手底下干活之前的事还记得吗
Before you were under me, you have any memories from before?
我有记忆  但是...
I have memories...
那不是真的  只是植入的
but they're not real. They're just implants.
跟我说说
Tell me one.
你小时候的事
From when you were a kid.
跟你说我的童年故事感觉有点怪
I feel strange sharing a childhood story,
因为我从来都没有童年
considering I was never a child.
如果我命令你说  会不会说出口
Well, would it help you share if I told you it was an order?
我小的时候有一个玩具
I have one about a toy that I had.
是一匹木马
A wooden horse.
下面还刻的有字
With an inscription underneath.
我只记得一群小男孩想从我手上抢走它
All I remember is a group of boys trying to take it away from me.
所以我跑了
So I run.
我要找地方把它藏起来
I go looking for a place to hide it,
只找到了一个黑暗的熔炉
and the only place is this dark furnace.
真的很黑  我很害怕
It's very dark, and I'm very scared...
但是我只有这匹小马  一定要把它藏起来
but this horse is all I have, so I go in anyway.
后来那群小孩找到了我
Later on, those kids find me...
还打我要我说小马在哪  但我不说
and they beat me to tell them where it is, but I don't.
就这样了
That's it.
小小的K为自己的东西而战
Little K, fighting for what's his.
很美好
It's a good one.
看着我
Look at me.
我们都在寻找某种真实
We're all just looking out for something real.
如果我喝醉了怎么办
What happens if I finish that?
不用去工作吗  长官
Shouldn't I get back to work, madam?
查了DNA向我汇报
Check back in after DNA base.
洛杉矶警局
DNA档案室
KD6-3.7警官
Officer KD6 - 3.7.
请求访问
Request.
2021年6月10日新生儿的DNA记录
DNA records children born 6-10-21.
输入日期
搜索异常现象
Looking for anomalies.
数据错误
能访问备份数据吗
You have the satcrystal backup?
错误：所有注解数据已被破坏  无法解读处理
好吧
Okay.
运行原始数据
Run it raw.
人由纯粹数据造就
Mere data makes a man.
A和C和T和G
A and C and T and G.
人类基因密码  只需这四个符号
The alphabet of you. All from four symbols.
我只有两个
I'm only two:
1和0
One and zero.
一半的符号  两倍的优雅  亲爱的
Half as much but twice as elegant, sweetheart.
不喜欢你的长官
You don't prefer your madam?
你听到了
You were listening.
也许吧
Maybe.
你不太喜欢她  没告诉她真相
You didn't like her enough to tell her the truth.
2021年6月10日
Six, 10 and 21.
没什么好说的
There's nothing to tell.
那个故事你跟我说过多少次了
How many times have you told me that story?
你的记忆
Your memory?
下面刻着的这个日期
The date carved beneath.
2021年6月10日
Six, 10 and 21.
是巧合吗
Coincidence?
是一个危险的巧合
A dangerous coincidence.
我一直知道你是特别的
I always knew you were special.
这就是特别之处
Maybe this is how.
一个孩子
A child.
女人生的孩子
Of woman born.
被扔进这个世界
Pushed into the world.
被需要
Wanted.
被爱
Loved.
如果这是真的
Well, if it were true...
接下来我就会被像我一样的人追捕一辈子
I'd be hunted for the rest of my life by someone just like me.
做做梦也没关系的
It's okay to dream a little.
-是不是  -我们不可以
- Isn't it? - Not if you're us.
停下
Stop.
4847号和2181号档案并排查撰
Put up 4847 and 2181 side-by-side.
完全相同  解读一下
They're identical. Translate.
女性
男性
一男一女
A boy and a girl.
-这不可能  -为什么
- It's impossible. - Why?
男性
两个人不可能有相同的DNA
Two people can't have identical DNA.
有一份不是真的  是个复本
One of these isn't real. It's a copy.
女性
男性
处理中心
莫瑞尔·科尔孤儿院
他们两个都在莫瑞尔·科尔孤儿院呆过
They were both processed at the Morrill Cole Orphanage.
女孩死在了那里
It says the girl died there.
得了遗传病
Genetic disorder.
迦拉太综合症
Galatians Syndrome.
那个男孩
And the boy...
失踪了
disappears.
孤儿院在哪里
Where's the orphanage?
你想去看看
You wanna go for a ride?
即将离开
大洛杉矶地区
洛杉矶废物处理厂
圣地亚哥区
好了  我们到了
Well, here we are.
安全带
Buckle up.
K
K?
K  K
K? K?
K  K  K
K? K? K?
都退后
Stay back.
继续开火
Fire again.
开火
Fire.
往东移动二百英尺
Two hundred feet to the east.
开火
Fire.
往北去
Go north.
开火
Fire.
停下  往东偏20度
Stop. Twenty degrees east.
停下
Stop.
放大点
Zoom in.
再放大
Closer.
噢  不是吧
Oh, come on.
起来啊
Get up.
站起来干你的活
Do your fucking job.
找到那孩子
Find the child.
看好车子
Watch the car.
能干活
Every last piece,
一片都不得漏掉  不然我就把你们扔出去
or I'll put you outside where the sky is raining...
让炸弹炸死你们
where it's raining fire!
你们是来干活的
You're in here to work.
如果你们不干活  要你们何用
And if you're not working, I don't need you.
我不要吃闲饭的--
I don't need any of--
这些镍都是殖民飞船用的
The nickel is for the colonial ships.
这是这些孩子...
Closest any of them or any of us is gonna get...
还有我们最接近外星殖民地好日子的时刻
to that grand life Off-world.
我鼓励他们玩耍  真的  一来找点事做
And I encourage play, I do. Keeps them occupied...
二来让手脚更灵活  对吧
and it makes them nimble, right?
都能干活
But it's work.
能干活的小孩才有活下去的价值
It's work that molds them into a child worth having.
你跟我说说吧
So come on, now.
你想要什么样的
What sort do you have in mind?
什么样的  我都有
Because I got all kinds.
-噢  不不不不  -我不买人
- Oh, no, no, no. - I'm not buying.
不不  这是我的生意  向来童叟无欺
No, no, no. This is just my game, and I play it fair.
不不  听着  有大人物...
No. No, I mean, bigger than you....
比你大的人物想让我关门都比你厉害
Bigger than you have tried to shut me down. Bigger than you.
他们  都是大人物
And they were men, at that.
大约30年前有个小男孩来到这里
A little boy came through here about 30 years back.
我要看当年的记录
I need to see your records.
合法收养  私人出售  我都要看
Legitimate placements, private sales, everything.
我没那么早的记录
Don't keep records that far back.
-你没有  -我没有
- You don't? - I don't.
对不起
Sorry.
帮不了你
Can't help you.
-帮不了  -对
- You can't? - Nope.
我看帮得了
I think you can.
你这样的人记性肯定相当好
I think someone like you keeps a long memory.
要么你老实告诉我
Now you can tell me what you remember...
要么我在你脑门上开个洞
or I can put a hole right here and take a look.
房间  他们在笑  你...你说什么来着
They were laughing and what was it you said? What'd you say?
你不来吗
Are you coming?
在哪呢
Where is it?
在哪呢  在哪呢  在哪呢
Oh, God.
这里
Where, where, where?
哪里  在哪里  在
I don't see it. Here.
不见了
It's gone.
一整年  一整年的都在
It's the entire year.
不是我干的
I didn't do that.
真的不是我
That wasn't me.
我没有  不是我
I didn't. Wasn't me.
我早就说了
I always told you.
你是特别的
You're special.
自然出生
Born.
不是制造的
Not made.
被小心地藏起来
Hidden with care.
你是真正的人了
A real boy now.
真正的人需要真正的名字
A real boy needs a real name.
乔
Joe.
"乔"
"Joe"?
K这个代号配不上你
You're too important for K.
你妈妈会给你起名字的
Your mother would've named you.
乔
Joe.
-乔  -别说了
- Joe. - Stop.
我怎么知道这是不是植入的记忆
How do I know if a memory is an implant or not?
谁制造的记忆
Who makes the memories?
安娜·斯特林博士
Dr. Ana Stelline?
有客人了
A visitor.
打扰你了
Is that okay?
没事
Yes.
很少有客人来
It's just unusual.
很高兴见到你  KD6-3.7警官
Nice to meet you, Officer KD6 - 3.7.
抱歉  这是个削弱的免疫系统
Sorry. It's a compromised immune system.
我做什么都行  只要不离开这个玻璃房
A life of freedom, so long as it's behind glass.
-所以你没去殖民地  -没错
- Is that why you're not Off-world? - Yes.
我的父母有外星通行证  但是我生病了
My parents had our passes in pocket, but I took sick.
所以  我的生活彻底改变了
So it was a new life for me.
然后  他们把我关进笼子里
And they put me in my cage...
还把我喜欢的东西都弄了进来
filled it with everything they could to keep me happy.
当然了 除了能陪我的人  我以前很爱热闹
Except company, of course. And I was used to crowds.
找我有什么事吗
What can I help you with?
我想有个案子你能帮上忙
Thought you might be able to help me with a case.
很少有人因为这么有意思的事
Oh, that's the most interesting thing
找我帮忙  很久了
I've been offered to help with in ages.
介不介意我  边说话边工作
Do you mind if I work while you talk?
不介意
Of course.
我可以听清楚每个字
I promise I hear every word.
他们说你是最好的记忆制造师
They say you're the best memory-maker there is.
好吧  他们过奖了
Well, then, they're kind.
我喜欢生日派对
I love birthday parties.
你为华莱士工作
You work for Wallace?
是他的供应商之一
Subcontract. I'm one of his suppliers.
他想雇佣我
He offered to buy me out,
但我不想连虚假的自由都没有
but I take my freedom where I can find it.
你是怎么做的
Why are you so good?
为什么你造的记忆这么真实
What makes your memories so authentic?
好吧  任何工作都需要一点想象力
Well, there's a bit of every artist in their work.
而且  我八岁起就被关在无菌室里
But I was locked in a sterile chamber at 8...
所以我想看这世界的话就只能靠想象
so if I wanted to see the world, I had to imagine it.
所以我非常擅长想象
Got very good at imagining.
华莱士利用我的才能保持产品稳定
Wallace needs my talent to maintain a stable product.
这是我们仅有的善意
I think it's only kind.
复制人的生活那么艰难  被迫做人类不想做的事
Replicants live such hard lives, made to do what we'd rather not.
我拯救不了你们的未来
I can't help your future...
但我可以给你们美好的回忆  和微笑
but I can give you good memories to think back on and smile.
这很好
It's nice.
不止是很好  它感觉很真实
It's better than nice. It feels authentic.
如果你有了真实的记忆
And if you have authentic memories,
那你就  有了真正的人类反应
you have real human responses.
你说是不是
Wouldn't you agree?
记忆都是编造的吗  你用过真实的记忆吗
Are they all constructed, or do you ever use ones that are real?
使用真实的记忆可是违法的  警官
It's illegal to use real memories, officer.
你是怎么辨别的
How can you tell the difference?
你能确定某事
Can you tell if something...
真的发生过
really happened?
他们以为细节多就是真的
They all think it's about more detail.
但记忆其实不是这样的
But that's not how memory works.
我们回忆的是感受
We recall with our feelings.
真实的记忆应该是混乱的
Anything real should be a mess.
亲眼看看吧
I can show you.
坐吧
Sit.
现在  想想你愿意让我看到的记忆
Now, think about the memory you want me to see.
不用太在意  心里想就行
Not even that hard. Just picture it.
只想一点
Let it play.
这是真实的记忆
Someone lived this, yes.
它发生过
This happened.
我知道是真的
I know it's real.
该死  混蛋
Goddamn it!
KD6-3.7号警官  警督让你回警局
Officer KD6 - 3.7. Madam is calling you in.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
放下武器  把手放在我能看见的地方
Drop your gun and keep your hands where I can see them.
-细胞  -细胞
- Cells. - Cells.
-你是否为某机构服务过  细胞  -细胞
- Have you ever been in an institution? Cells. - Cells
不执行任务时
When you're not performing your duties,
-他们是否把你关进小房间里  细胞  -细胞
- do they keep you in a little box? Cells. - Cells.
-相连  -相连
- Interlinked. - Interlinked.
握着你所爱之人的手是何感觉
What's it like to hold the hand of someone you love?
-相连  -相连
- Interlinked. - Interlinked.
-细胞之间相连  -细胞之间相连
- Within cells interlinked. - Within the cells interlinked.
-恐怖  -恐怖
- Dreadfully. - Dreadfully.
检测到异常
-被恐怖笼罩是什么感觉  恐怖  -恐怖
- What's it like to be filled with dread? Dreadfully. - Dreadfully.
-你喜欢与他人隔离吗  分明  -分明
- Do you like being separated from other people? Distinct. - Distinct.
-界限分明  -界限分明  黑暗  -黑暗
- Dreadfully distinct. Dark. - Dreadfully distinct. Dark.
-细胞之间相连  -细胞之间相连
- Within cells interlinked. - Within the cells interlinked.
-主干再相连  -主干再相连
- Within one stem. - Within one stem.
-趁着那恐怖的黑暗  -趁着那恐怖的黑暗
- And dreadfully distinct. - And dreadfully distinct.
-分明可见  -分明可见
- Against the dark. - Against the dark.
洁白水柱向上高喷  -洁白水柱向上高喷
A tall white fountain played.
你距离基准线非常远
You're not even close to baseline.
出去  把门关上
Out! And close the door.
你到底有什么毛病
What the fuck is with you?
我把这案子交给你
I put you on a case.
我特地告诉过你这件事有多重要
I impressed on you the importance of that case...
结果你竟然跑到什么升级中心闲逛
and then we pick you up fucking around outside an upgrade center?
扫描结果说你的脑子出问题了
Scan said you didn't look like you on the inside.
大幅度偏离基准线
Miles off your baseline.
-知道这是什么意思吗  -那孩子找到了
- Do you know what that means? - I found the kid.
他以标准复制人的身份手续生活工作
He was set up like a standard Replicant, put on a service job.
他不知道自己是谁
Even he didn't know who he was.
-然后  -然后解决了
- And? - And it's done.
-什么叫"解决了"  -按你的命令
- What does that mean, "It's done"? - What you asked.
解决了
It's done.
见鬼
Fuck.
你刚刚阻止了一场战争
You just stopped a bomb from going off.
做得很好
You did good.
我可以让你安全离开这里
I can help you get out of this station alive...
但48小时后你必须恢复正常
but you have 48 hours to get back on track.
把你的枪和警徽交出来
Surrender your gun and badge.
下一次基准测试我会交给别人
And your next baseline test is out of my hands.
谢谢  长官
Thank you, madam.
你说对了
You were right.
你从没说错过
You were right about everything.
我还以为你没兴趣呢  工作狂
Thought you weren't interested, worky man.
你喜欢她  我看得出来
You liked her. I could tell.
没关系的
It's okay.
我想给你
She's real.
真实的感受
I wanna be real for you.
对我来说你是真的
You are real for me.
你有个特别的女朋友
You have a special lady here.
好了
Okay.
开始吧
Let's do it.
真奇妙啊
Look at you.
安静点  我要同步
Quiet now, I have to sync.
乔伊满足您的一切幻想
Joi is anything you want her to be.
乔伊伴您走遍天涯海角
Joi goes anywhere you want her to go.
系使用99.9%解毒液
99.9 percent detoxified water.
是木头做的
It's from a tree.
没你的事了
I'm done with you.
你可以走了
You can go now.
安静点
Quiet now.
我也当过你了
I've been inside you.
倒是没觉得有什么特别的
Not so much there as you think.
咖啡
Coffee?
很快会有人来抓我
They'll be coming after me soon.
我跟你一起走
I'm coming with you.
但不能这样走
But not like this.
如果他们真来这里抓你
If they come here looking for you,
一定会读取我所有的内存
they'll have access to all my memories.
你要把我从控制台上删除
You have to delete me from the console.
我的礼物
My present.
把我放那里
Put me there.
我不能这样做
I can't do that.
你想想看
Think about it:
如果装置出了意外你就完了
If anything happens to this, that's it.
你会消失
You're gone.
是的
Yes.
像真正的那个人
Like a real girl.
求你了
Please.
乔  求你了
Joe, please.
我想这样做
I want this.
但是我自己做不了
But I can't do it myself.
破坏追踪器
Break the antenna.
竟然是真木头  你真有钱  哥们
我可以给你弄匹真马
你要真马吗
我不需要真的马
I don't need a real horse.
我能给你弄一匹  华莱士那种
我不需要真的马  我只想  只想知道它的来历
I don't need a real horse. I just wanna find out where it's from.
闻起来像旧尘土
但结构很新
是不是因为被辐射过
Radiation from a reactor?
不  衰变得更多
氚
很旧  很旧
符合脏弹辐射值
It matches a dirty bomb.
只有一个地方受过这么强的辐射
就一个地方辐射这么强
There's only one place that dirty.
那里没人住
Nobody lives there.
你问我它是从哪来的
我已经告诉你了
你还想怎样呢
马  羊
外星殖民地的手续
不管你要什么  巴基博士都能帮你搞到
四倍
Four
往左偏30度
30 degrees to the left.
往前移
Tilt up.
上升到400英尺
Elevate to 400 feet.
辐射分析
Radiation analysis.
往前
Move forward.
阳台
Tilt up.
停下
Stop.
往前移
Move forward.
放大五倍
Go to five.
七倍  往前移
Seven, move forward.
六倍
Six.
停下
Stop.
放大七倍
Go to seven.
八倍
Eight.
九倍
Nine.
热量分析
Heat analysis.
有生命
Life.
是什么
What is it?
马上就能知道了
Guess we're about to find out.
这里太黑了
Too dark in here.
我喜欢他
I like him.
他在哪
He's a good boy.
告诉我
Where is he?
我不知道  他下班了
I have no idea. He's off-duty.
你再找找
Check around.
我找了
I checked...
可能去的地方都找了
...anywhere a good boy might go.
你来晚了
You're too late.
结束了
It's gone.
他解决了
He destroyed it.
对了  除了你之前
Everything about it.
拿走的那一箱骨头
Well, except for the box of bones that you already took.
我敢打赌  你嫌不够  所以才来
Which, I'll wager, wasn't enough. Here you are.
你这个小东西
You tiny thing.
面对革命性的新事物  你只想杀死他吗
In the face of the fabulous new, your only thought is to kill it?
就因为害怕巨变吗
For fear of great change?
螳臂还想挡车  你妄想
You can't hold the tide with a broom.
可惜我挡住了
Except that I did.
他在哪里
Where is he?!
你就这么肯定
You're so sure.
因为是他说的
Because he told you.
因为我们不撒谎
Because we never lie.
我会告诉华莱士先生  你先想杀我
I'm gonna tell Mr. Wallace you tried to shoot me first.
所以我只能杀了你
So I had to kill you.
那你就动手吧
Then do what you gotta do.
遵命
Madam.
确定KD6-3.7号警官位置
Officer KD6 - 3.7.
你不会碰巧身上带了一块奶酪吧
Mightn't happen to have a piece of cheese about you, now?
是吗  小子
Would you, boy?
《金银岛》
Treasure Island?
你看书
He reads.
非常好
That's good.
我也是
Me too.
晚上除了看看书也没别的事了
Not much else to do around here at night anymore.
我时常在夜晚梦到奶酪
Many is the night I dream of cheese...
大多是烤过的
toasted, mostly.
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
我听到钢琴声
I heard the piano.
别撒谎
Don't lie.
没礼貌
It's rude.
你是警察
You're a cop.
-我不是来抓你的  -是吗
- I'm not here to take you in. - Oh, yeah?
那干什么
Then, what?
我只想问你几个问题
I just have some questions.
问什么问题
What questions?
待着
Stay.
听着  我不想伤害你
Look, I don't wanna hurt you.
但你是在逼我动手
But you're not making it easy.
我喜欢这首歌
I like this song.
我们可以继续打  或者去喝一杯
We could keep at this, or we could get a drink.
我想去喝一杯
I'll take the drink.
这地方真不错
This is really something.
整个小镇都不错
The whole town was something.
可惜没了
One time.
忘记烦心事
Forget your troubles...
看看表演
...see a show...
小赌一两把
...gamble a little.
这次赢点下次输点
Win some money, lose some money.
那些色子搞得就像糖果
They made money seem like candy.
你喝威士忌吗
You like whiskey?
我这多的是
I've got millions...
数不清有多少瓶
...of bottles of whiskey.
给
Here.
流血了
Bleeding.
它是真的
Is it real?
我不知道
I don't know.
问它吧
Ask him.
你叫什么
You got a name?
KD6-3.7号警官
Officer KD6 - 3.7--
这不叫名字  这叫序列号
That's not a name. That's a serial number.
好吧
All right.
乔
Joe.
你想怎样  乔
What do you want, Joe?
-我想问你几个问题  -比如说
- I wanna ask you some questions. - Like what?
比如她的名字  你孩子的母亲
Like what was her name, the mother of your child?
她长什么样
What was she like?
-你们俩住在这吗  -你的问题太多了
- You two live here together? - Too many questions.
我做过这种活  做得很好
I had your job. I was good at it.
-当时很简单  -为什么现在要搞复杂
- It was simpler then. - Why you making it complicated?
-你为什么不回答问题  -什么问题
- Why don't you answer the question? - What question?
你不像是那种会逃避问题的人
I didn't figure you as one for bullshit.
她叫什么名字
What's her name?
瑞秋
Rachael.
她名叫瑞秋
Her name was Rachael.
那孩子怎么了
What happened to the kid?
谁把他送进孤儿院的  是你吗
Who put it in the orphanage? Was it you?
那时我早就走了
I was long gone by then.
你没见过自己的孩子
You didn't even meet your own kid?
为什么
Why?
因为这是计划好的
Because that was the plan.
我告诉他们如何篡改记录  掩盖所有痕迹
I showed them how to scramble the records, cover their tracks.
大家都有任务  我的任务是离开
Everyone had a part. Mine was to leave.
然后就是大停电  毁了所有资料
Then the Blackout came, paved over everything.
即使我想找也找不到孩子了
Couldn't have found the child if I tried.
-那你想找吗  -我不想
- Did you want to? - Not really.
-为什么  -因为当时我们被人追杀
- Why not? - Because we were being hunted.
我不想让我们的孩子被发现
I didn't want our child found...
被分解  被解剖
taken apart, dissected.
有时候如果你爱一个人
Sometimes, to love someone...
就要当个陌生人
you gotta be a stranger.
敬陌生人
To strangers.
你干了什么
What'd you do?
你带谁来了
Who'd you bring?
-我没带  -是吗
- No one. - Oh, yeah?
锁定目标
Target locked.
他们知道你在这
They know you're here.
我自己来的
I came alone.
坏孩子
Bad dog.
不要
Stop.
我真希望你满意我们的产品
I do hope you're satisfied with our product.
我爱你
I love--
嘿  有个人很想见见你
Hey, there's someone who wants to meet you.
你可以信任我们
You can trust us.
你一定想让我往上看再往左看
You must want me to look up and to the left.
这是福瑞莎
This is Freysa.
萨珀在卡兰星的战友
She fought with Sapper on Calantha.
我认识你的脸
I recognize you.
你帮他把孩子藏起来了
Did you help him hide the child?
我当时也在
I was there.
亲眼看到奇迹降生
I saw a miracle delivered.
那个孩子对着我嚎啕大哭
A perfect little face crying up at me.
脾气可真大啊
Mad as thunder.
你陪着她
Were you with her?
瑞秋
Rachael?
她死在了我怀里
I held her as she died.
我们藏起孩子  发誓要终生保守这个秘密
We hid the child and made a vow to keep our secret.
所以萨珀宁愿死在你手里
That's why Sapper let you kill him.
我知道  那孩子意味着我们不仅仅是奴隶
I knew that baby meant we are more than just slaves.
如果复制人能孕育生命
If a baby can come from one of us...
那我们就是自己的主人
we are our own masters.
比人类更像人类
More human than humans.
革命就要开始了
A revolution is coming.
我们正在组建军队
And we're building an army.
我想解放我们的同类
I want to free our people.
如果你想要自由
If you want to be free...
就加入我们
join us.
戴克  萨珀  你  我...
Deckard, Sapper, you, me...
跟这场风暴相比  我们的性命不值一提
our lives mean nothing next to a storm that's coming.
为解救同类而死  是我们最具人性的选择
Dying for the right cause is the most human thing we can do.
你引华莱士抓了戴克
You led Wallace to Deckard.
你不能让戴克引华莱士过来抓我
You cannot allow Deckard to lead Wallace to me.
所以你必须杀了戴克
You must kill Deckard.
戴克只希望他的女儿平平安安
Deckard only wanted his baby to be safe.
她很安全
And she is.
等时机来临  我会说出她的存在...
When the time comes, I will show her to the world...
让她带领我们的军队
and she will lead our army.
女儿
"She"?
当然了
Of course.
瑞秋生了个女儿
Rachael had a daughter.
我亲眼看着她来到这个世界
With my own eyes, I saw her come.
送走她时  我还给她穿上了蓝色的衣服
I dressed her in blue when it was time for her to go.
你藏的是个男孩
It was a boy that you hid.
那个男孩只是一个疑兵之计
That is just a piece of the puzzle.
你以为那个孩子是你
You imagined it was you?
你错了
You did.
我们都希望是自己
We all wish it was us.
她是我们的信仰
That's why we believe.
这是真实的记忆
Someone lived this, yes.
我告诉他们如何篡改记录  掩盖所有痕迹
I showed them how to scramble the records, cover their tracks.
我亲眼看着她来到这个世界
With my own eyes, I saw her come.
送走她时  我还给她穿上了蓝色衣服
I dressed her in blue when it was time for her to go.
任何工作都需要一点想象力
There's a bit of every artist in their work.
那一个经常跳出来
Always jumping, that one.
从没想过落到岸上的怎么办
Never a thought of what to do if it made land.
即便有天大的勇气  也改变不了事实
All the courage in the world cannot alter fact.
我在很久之前就想见见你了
I have wanted to meet you for so very long.
你真是个奇迹  戴克先生
You are a wonder to me, Mr. Deckard.
我有一把锁
I had the lock.
我找到了钥匙
I found the key.
但是锁簧对不齐  所以门还是打不开
Yet the pins do not align. The door remains locked.
我需要一个样本  帮我解决这个问题
I need the specimen to reach it, Mr. Deckard.
那孩子
The child.
我需要那孩子
I need the child.
我将亲手放飞他们
To teach them all to fly.
于是神顾念瑞秋
And God remembered Rachel...
应允了她  使她能生育
heeded her and opened her womb.
喜欢这只鹰吗
Do you like our owl?
■
泰瑞公司档案
2019年11月20日
它是人造的
It's artificial?
当然是人造的
Of course it is.
肯定很贵吧
Must be expensive.
很贵  我是瑞秋
Very. I'm Rachael.
■
泰瑞公司档案
2019年11月20日
我是戴克
Deckard.
这是不是
Is it the same...
那天你和她
...now, as then...
初遇的那一刻
...the moment you met her?
这些年来你从未忘怀那一天
All these years you looked back on that day...
一直沉醉在那完美的一刻
drunk on the memory of its perfection.
她那鲜嫩的嘴唇
How shiny her lips.
那瞬间迸发的火花
How instant your connection.
难道你没有想过
Did it never occur to you
这就是选你执行任务的原因
that's why you were summoned in the first place?
脑中的指令
Designed to do nothing short of fall
让你在看到她的第一眼就爱上她
for her right then and there.
一切都是为了制造  完美的  样本
All to make that single perfect specimen.
当然了  前提是真有指令
That is, if you were designed.
爱情
Love...
抑或是精准的设计
or mathematical precision.
是
Yes.
不是
No.
我知道那是真的
I know what's real.
把自己蒙在鼓里这一招非常聪明
It was very clever to keep yourself empty of information...
而代价是放弃所爱的一切
and all it cost you was everything.
但是依然能帮我
But you can still help me.
你当时  在其中出力了
You had help in the hiding.
他们去哪了
Where did they go?
你肯定知道什么
I know you know something.
告诉我
Help me...
我保证我绝不会亏待你的
and very, very good things can come to you.
你没有孩子
You don't have children...
对吗
do you?
我有几百万个孩子
Oh, I have millions.
你以为我只能用痛苦来威胁你
You think I have nothing to offer but pain.
只有我知道
Only I know...
你热爱痛苦
you love pain.
痛苦能够提醒你曾经的喜悦是真的
Pain reminds you the joy you felt was real.
先来点喜悦吧
More joy, then.
请不要害怕
Do not be afraid.
一个天使...
An angel...
两次制造
made again.
为你
For you.
你想我吗
Did you miss me?
你不爱我吗
Don't you love me?
她是绿色眼睛
Her eyes were green.
在殖民地
Off-world...
我有的是办法能让你开口
I have everything I need to make you talk.
你还不知道什么是痛苦
You do not know what pain is yet.
你会知道的
You will learn.
你好  帅哥
Hello, handsome.
今天很累  嗯
What a day.
孤单一人吗
You look lonely.
我可以陪你
I can fix that.
你看起来像个好人啊
You look like a good joe.
乔伊
听你想听的 看你想看的
为解救同类而死  是我们最具人性的选择
Dying for the right cause is the most human thing we can do.
因为你们从未见过奇迹
Because you've never seen a miracle.
您正在进入洛杉矶机场禁飞区域
You're entering Los Angeles Airport restricted airspace.
请验证身份
Confirm your identity.
S144XD号飞行员  已验证
Transport S-14-4-XD. Confirmed.
这里是6号机
Space, this is 0-6.
出港  起飞  030航线
Outbound departure, route 0-3-0.
我们要去哪
Where are we going?
回家
Home.
警告
Warning.
-能到地方吗  -高度不够
- Can we make it? - We're too low!
我们飞回去
Take us back!
给我升高
Get us up.
打开舱门
Open the door.
我是最优秀的
I'm the best one.
殖民地还等着呢
Off-world is waiting.
乔  乔
Joe. Joe!
乔
Joe!
你应该让我死在那
You should have let me die out there.
你死了
You did.
淹死在那儿了
You drowned out there.
你可以去见你的女儿了
You're free to meet your daughter now.
美好的回忆都是她的
All the best memories are hers.
你是谁
Why?
为什么帮我
Who am I to you?
去见你的女儿吧
Go meet your daughter.
你还好吗
You okay?
稍等一会
Just a moment.
是不是很美
Beautiful, isn't it?
导演 丹尼斯·维伦纽瓦
编剧 汉普顿·范彻  迈克尔·格林
故事 汉普顿·范彻
美国艾肯传媒集团 出品
美国哥伦比亚电影公司 联合出品
英国雷德利·斯科特工作室 制作
美国艾肯娱乐公司 制作
美国巴德·约金工作室 制作
美国托里登影片公司 与 16:14娱乐 联合制作
丹尼斯·维伦纽瓦 电影作品
瑞恩·高斯林
哈里森·福特
银
翼
杀
手
改编自 菲利普·K·迪克 小说
《仿生人会梦见电子羊吗？》
制片人 安德鲁·A·科索夫  布罗德里克·约翰逊
制片人 巴德·约金  辛西娅·塞克斯·约金
执行制片 雷德利·斯科特
执行制片 比尔·卡拉罗
执行制片
蒂姆·甘博 弗兰克·吉斯特拉
耶鲁·巴迪克 瓦尔·希尔
联合执行制片
伊恩·迈克葛罗音 阿沙·格林伯格
联合制片
卡尔·O·罗杰斯
阿沙·格林伯格
史蒂文·P·瓦格纳
摄影指导 罗杰·狄金斯
艺术指导 丹尼斯·盖斯纳
剪辑 乔·沃克
视觉特效 约翰·尼尔森
服装设计 蕾妮·爱普勒
音乐
本杰明·沃菲斯齐 汉斯·季默
瑞安娜·德·阿玛斯
西尔维娅·侯克斯
罗宾·莱特
麦肯兹·戴维斯
卡拉·朱里
连尼·詹姆斯
肖恩·杨
爱德华·詹姆斯·奥莫斯
戴夫·巴蒂斯塔
杰瑞德·莱托
巴哈德·阿布迪
西娅姆·阿巴斯
伍德·哈里斯
大卫·达斯马齐连
选角导演 弗兰辛·梅思勒
音乐监督 戴瓦·安德森
音效剪辑 马克·曼吉尼
音效设计 席奥·格林